<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Hello, my name is Samuel and I&amp;rsquo;m a platform engineer, cloud engineer, and DevOps professional. I&amp;rsquo;m originally from Australia and moved to Germany in 2015 to pursue my career in technology. Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve gained extensive experience and have established myself as a respected professional in the industry.
Throughout my professional experience, I have worked with cutting-edge technologies in cloud computing, software development, and infrastructure management. As a platform engineer, I design and implement scalable, reliable, and secure platforms that enable organizations to deliver their products and services to customers.</description></item><item><title>Getting to know ChatGPT</title><link>/posts/chatgpt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/chatgpt/</guid><description>Hello everyone! Today, I want to share my intriguing journey of adapting a pre-made Python tutorial on building a URL shortener to use DynamoDB for its backend, and how I successfully crafted a unique, user-friendly frontend with the help of ChatGPT.
As someone who has always been captivated by the simplicity and usefulness of URL shorteners, I wanted to create my own but with a personal touch. I knew that in order to achieve a functional, secure, and scalable URL shortener, I would need a strong backend, an engaging frontend, and an efficient infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Apps</title><link>/apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apps/</guid><description>Shortly - URL shortening api shortly api shortly ui</description></item></channel></rss>